Pixie Hollow Games is a animation, family film directed by Bradley Raymond.
Rosetta and new arrival Chloe band together to try to break the garden fairies' legendary losing streak in the Pixie
Hollow Games, a sports spectacle filled with pixie pageantry, fantastic fairy events and hilarious surprises.
Rosetta (voice), played by Megan Hilty.
Glimmer (voice), played by Tiffany Thornton.
Fern (voice), played by Zendaya.
Rumble (voice), played by Jason Dolley.
Chloe (voice), played by Brenda Song.
Tinker Bell (voice), played by Mae Whitman.
Pixie Hollow Games is a 23-minute animated television special
broadcast on November 19, 2011, on Disney Channel.
Based on the Disney Fairies franchise, it was produced by
Disneytoon Studios and animated by Prana Studios.
It features the voices of Mae Whitman, Lucy Liu, Raven-Symoné, Megan Hilty, Angela Bartys, and others, as Tinker
Bell and the other fairies of Pixie Hollow in Never Land, taking part in an Olympic-style competition.
It is based loosely on J.
Barrie's Peter Pan stories, by way of Disney's animated adaptation.
It was originally intended as the last of five feature-length films in the Tinker Bell series of direct-to-DVD 3D
animated films, with the title Tinker Bell: Race through the Seasons, and a release date in 2012.
However, the movie was rescheduled and retooled as a TV
special instead of a film-length movie.
Unlike the previous feature films in this series, Tinker Bell is not a central
featured character in this special release, which is focused on Rosetta.
The film explores themes of sports, magic,
competition, fairy tale, olympic games.